那你多少次让4万伏的电流流经他的身体
And how many times did you send 40,000 volts through his body?
反对  法官阁下
Objection, Your Honor.
电棍的电压设置为4万伏
The stun gun is set at 40,000,
但是当探头接触到皮肤时
but when the probes make contact with the skin,
会降低至1400伏
the voltage drops to 1,400.
如果我在哈佛上的物理课没记错的话
If I remember my Harvard physics class correctly,
迪菲尔德先生  你说的对  反对有效
Mr. Deerfield, I believe you're right. Sustained.
1400伏
1,400 volts.
好像那就不难受了
That's much better.
住手  泰勒
Stop it! Tyler.
你能呼吸吗  你能呼吸吗
Can you breathe? Can you breathe?
你用1400伏的电压猛击了他多少次
How many times did you jolt him with 1,400 volts?
三次
Three times.
当你第三次用1400伏的电压攻击他后
And what happened after you shot him
发生了什么事
the third time with 1,400 volts?